<root>
    <item> 
       <title>Himanshu is enjoying Math and English</title> 
       <link>http://jyoti.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=497</link> 
       <img src="images/Himanshu.JPG" lowsrc="images/Himanshu-468x480.jpg" /> 
       <text>Himanshu is an 8 year old boy studying in second grade at Amar Jyoti School.  He has a a pleasant personality and is regular in coming to school. Himanshu's family makes very little money. His father is an auto rickshaw driver. Despite their low income, his parents are keen to educate him.  His father attends PTA meetings...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Ramnabai can finally cook in a lit up kitchen!</title> 
       <link>http://trf.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=73</link> 
       <img src="images/IMG_0489-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/IMG_0489-300x225.jpg" /> 
       <text>Darkness gave way to light when a solar lantern entered the home of Ramnabai thanks to Cooler Planet and the efforts of The Restoring Force.  Prior to this donation, Ramnabai had lived her entire life without electricity. Each evening, she hurried home from the fields to prepare dinner before the sun set and darkness enveloped the...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Subash is now working with his welding kit!</title> 
       <link>http://padma.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=259</link> 
       <img src="images/subash-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/subash-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>B. Subash Chandra Bose is the son of Mr.Baskar, a farmer coolie and Ms.Kowsalya, a home maker. He has a no brothers, but he has a sister who is married. He is from Sengalipuram village in Tiruvarur dist. Thank you very much Zanoon for your generous donation of a welding kit!</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>A bright future!</title> 
       <link>http://jyoti.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=144</link> 
       <img src="images/babloo.jpg" lowsrc="images/babloo-479x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Babaloo is a student of Nursery class of Amar Jyoti School. He is a newly admitted child and trying his best to adjust to the school environment. Babaloo belongs to an economically underprivileged family and both the parents work hard to make their ends meet. His father works as a laborer and his mother is...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>What's in the home garden?</title> 
       <link>http://ghi.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=25</link> 
       <img src="images/homegarden.jpg" lowsrc="images/homegarden-300x200.jpg" /> 
       <text>Though it depends on the season and the needs of individual families, the home garden package generally includes a combination of the following:
 
Moringa tree
Fruit tree seedling (papaya or avocado)
Amaranth
Cowpea
Sunflower
Neem
Tephrosia
Garlic
Tomatoes
Carrots
Beets
Swiss Chard
Kale
Sweet Pepper
Eggplant
 
</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>"Seeing is believing" - Dr Uma Tuli  - Founder Amar Jyoti</title> 
       <link>http://jyoti.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=133</link> 
       <img src="images/oadrggcvpq0jju04bmm7cqnuo1_500.jpg" lowsrc="images/oadrggcvpq0jju04bmm7cqnuo1_500-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Amarjyoti is a unique school where you will see physically challenged children hand in hand with their able bodied friends -- laughing, playing and learning together!</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Chandaben is joyful to see her grandchildren again</title> 
       <link>http://bpa.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=339</link> 
       <img src="images/Chandaben-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/Chandaben-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Chandaben is 65 years old, residing at Sahij village, in the district of Kalol, India. She is a housewife. In villages, people are not aware of the dangers of cataracts and often become needlessly blind. Chandaben had a cataract in her left eye due to her age but could not afford surgery. With the support...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Udaysinh has a shop on wheels!</title> 
       <link>http://bpa.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=789</link> 
       <img src="images/Udaysinh-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/Udaysinh-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Udaysinh A.Parmar is 45 years old and lives in a little village 45 miles from Ahmedabad. Udaysinh lost the use of both of his legs at birth. His polio kept him from completing his education. When he heard of BPA and their free distribution of tricycle, he applied for one.  Thanks to Amit's donation, he...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Lalit's tution has been sponsored for 1 month</title> 
       <link>http://jyoti.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=124</link> 
       <img src="images/children-at-work.jpg" lowsrc="images/children-at-work-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Lalit is an enthusiastic student in the nursery class at Amar Jyoti School. His father's income is inadequate to pay Lalit's school fees, but a generous donation has helped sponsor 1 month of tuition. See Your Impact is hoping to sponsor Lalit for a full year.</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Rani is new to Amar Jyoti!</title> 
       <link>http://jyoti.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=508</link> 
       <img src="images/Rani_Kushwah.jpg" lowsrc="images/Rani_Kushwah-480x376.jpg" /> 
       <text>Rani is 10 years old  and is studying in first grade at Amar Jyoti. She is regular in coming to school and enjoys learning new things. Rani's family makes very little money.  Her father is a laborer and her mother is a housewife.  Despite their low income, they are very motivated to send to her to school...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Shailesh can now express himself</title> 
       <link>http://naftb.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=73</link> 
       <img src="images/img_0068.jpg" lowsrc="images/img_0068-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>12 year-old Shailesh Damor wants to say thank you to a man he's never met. Shailesh's family lives on less than $1 a day. Because he is blind, he requires special education at the Blind People's Association school. At school he is encouraged to express himself through writing, which requires a Braille Writing Frame...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Now R. Vijay has the Electrical Kit!</title> 
       <link>http://padma.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=213</link> 
       <img src="images/Video-58-00m-05s.jpg" lowsrc="images/Video-58-00m-05s-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>R. Vijay is the youngest son of Mr. Ravi, a farmer and Ms. Suseela, a home maker. He has 2 brothers who are both masons. He is from Aandiyoor near Nannilam in Tiruvarur Dist. Thank you very much Mr.Francisco for providing the kit that can allow him to continue his studies!</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Kamruddin practices writing at Amar Jyoti School</title> 
       <link>http://jyoti.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=275</link> 
       <img src="images/Kamruddin-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/Kamruddin-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Kamruddin is an 11 year old boy studying in the Hearing Impaired section at Amar Jyoti School. He is performing at 1st grade level in academics. He has been coming to Amar Jyoti School since March 3, 2008. He is a pleasant child and is punctual in coming to school. He is hearing impaired but...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Tayyaba Zain is working hard!</title> 
       <link>http://jyoti.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=287</link> 
       <img src="images/Tayyaba-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/Tayyaba-479x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Tayyaba is a 10 year old girl studying in the Multiple Disability Section at Amar Jyoti School. Tayyaba is a mentally challenged girl. She suffered from jaundice when she was one and a half months old and suffered from thyroid problem at the age of six months. To date, she is getting medications and...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title> Abhijeet Sarkar is working hard at Amar Jyoti School</title> 
       <link>http://jyoti.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=283</link> 
       <img src="images/Abhijeet-Sarkar-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/Abhijeet-Sarkar-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Abhijeet Sarkar is a six year old boy studying in the Multiple Disability section at Amar Jyoti School. He has been coming to Amar Jyoti since January, 2008. He has Down Syndrome and some problems with walking. Despite these issues, Abhijeet is eager to come to school and get involved in different activities. Abhijeet comes from...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>B. Ambedkar has a new two wheeler repair kit</title> 
       <link>http://padma.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=494</link> 
       <img src="images/ambedkar.jpg" lowsrc="images/ambedkar-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>B. Ambedkar is from a family of agricultural workers. His father, Mr. Balakrishnan, is a farm laborer and Ms. Usha is a home maker. He has a brother studying in 7th standard (grade) and a sister studying in 6th standard. B. Ambedkar has always had a keen interest in automobile mechanics which helped inspire him...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Kousalya is a great English student!</title> 
       <link>http://isha.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=39</link> 
       <img src="images/kousalya-768x1024.jpg" lowsrc="images/kousalya-225x300.jpg" /> 
       <text>Kousalya is 9 years old and is in 4th grade at the Isha Vidhya School in Erode, a small town in rural Tamil Nadu in southern India.  Kousalya’s father is a motor mechanic and her mother is a housewife. They first enrolled Kousalya at Isha Vidhya in 2007, when she was entering 2nd grade...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Sagar is back at Amar Jyoti!</title> 
       <link>http://jyoti.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=435</link> 
       <img src="images/Sagar_Saini.JPG" lowsrc="images/Sagar_Saini-480x347.jpg" /> 
       <text>Sagar is a 14 year old boy studying in 2nd standard (second grade) at Amar Jyoti School.  At a young age, he contracted polio in his right leg.  He is a social, well mannered boy.  Sagar comes from an economically under privileged family. His father is a garland maker and only earns daily wages. Sagar and...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>A new lantern has helped Vandana improve her grades!</title> 
       <link>http://trf.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=18</link> 
       <img src="images/Seeyourimpact-0071-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/Seeyourimpact-0071-300x225.jpg" /> 
       <text>Thanks to a very generous donation of a solar lantern,  Vandana has been able to spend more time on her studies and improve her grades.  This year, her first year in her BA program, she received an overall score of 80%.  In 12th grade, he was only able to score 70%, as her studies were...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Krishan will start first grade!</title> 
       <link>http://jyoti.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=362</link> 
       <img src="images/Krishna-Kushwah-768x1024.jpg" lowsrc="images/Krishna-Kushwah-360x480.jpg" /> 
       <text>Krishan is a ten year old boy studying in the special section at Amar Jyoti School. Despite his Cerebral Palsy, he is motivated to come to school and is making sincere efforts to improve his performance. He has been coming to Amar Jyoti for two years. Krishan comes from an economically underprivileged family. His father is...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Hemant loves art!</title> 
       <link>http://jyoti.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=489</link> 
       <img src="images/Hemant.JPG" lowsrc="images/Hemant-480x368.jpg" /> 
       <text>Hemant is a 14 year old boy studying in fifth grade at Amar Jyoti School. He is affected by polio in both of his legs and as a result, he must walk with the help of crutches.  Hemant comes from an economically underprivileged family. The only source of income for the family comes from his father...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Securing a better life</title> 
       <link>http://padma.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/2009/09/03/venkatesan-has-the-electrical-kit/</link> 
       <img src="images/manikandan-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/manikandan-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Venkatesan grew up in a household that lived on less t han $1 a day. He is determined to secure a better life for himself by learning a trade. Thanks to a generous contribution, Venkatesan now has the electrical kit required for his schooling. He looks forward to completing his training and getting a job.</text> 
   </item>   
   <item> 
       <title>Jabirmiya can now support his family!</title> 
       <link>http://bpa.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=451</link> 
       <img src="images/IMG_0304-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/IMG_0304-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Shaikh Jabirmiya Alladin first contracted polio at the age of 2 years. By the age of 30 he had completed his board exams, and was sitting idly at home in his village of Billaj in the Kheda District.  Jabirmiya is the eldest in his family, with two little sisters and one younger brother, and he...</text> 
   </item>  
   <item> 
       <title>The Solar Lantern Project</title> 
       <link>http://trf.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=31</link> 
       <img src="images/Lantern-Photos-0031-785x1024.jpg" lowsrc="images/Lantern-Photos-0031-230x300.jpg" /> 
       <text>Mission of the Solar Lantern Project: To bring light and thereby prosperity into the lives of people living in remote villages. This pilot project explores the possibility of creating a social change in the life of very poor people who live in remote villages, where there is little or no electricity and no...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Now Kannan can work to support his family!</title> 
       <link>http://padma.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=542</link> 
       <img src="images/kannan.jpg" lowsrc="images/kannan-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Kannan, the youngest son in his family, originally joined the Padma Industrial School to increase his family's income level.  He has 2 older brothers, both of whom work as farm laborers.  He also has an older sister who is married.   Successful completion of the welding course at Padma would allow Kannan to earn as...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>G. Mohanraj has a new welding kit!</title> 
       <link>http://padma.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=448</link> 
       <img src="images/Mohanraj.jpg" lowsrc="images/Mohanraj-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>After completing 10th grade, G. Mohanraj joined the Padma Industrial School to learn welding. He wants to increase his family income level and support his parents and siblings. His father, Mr. Govindaraj is a farm laborer and his mother, Ms.Vijaya, is a home maker.  He has 3 sisters.  Two have completed their schooling and one...</text> 
   </item>  
   <item> 
       <title>Success and Swiss Chard</title> 
       <link>http://ghi.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=45</link> 
       <img src="images/Success-and-Swiss-Chard-1.jpg" lowsrc="images/Success-and-Swiss-Chard-1-193x300.jpg" /> 
       <text>Frederick lives with his family in the middle of Kigali, but despite being in the center of the city, and with only a small plot of land, he has become an avid gardener. With the help of Gardens for Health, he now has the best home garden in his neighborhood. He was recently recognized by...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Durgesh can now study at night!</title> 
       <link>http://trf.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=24</link> 
       <img src="images/Durgesh2.jpg" lowsrc="images/Durgesh2-300x226.jpg" /> 
       <text>14 year old Durgesh is thrilled to have a new solar lantern that will improve his quality of life!  Durgesh lives just outside the city of Gurgaon, and is the son of a day laborer.  Durgesh and his father live in a temporary home without electricity.  Before receiving the solar lantern, Durgesh struggled to complete...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Jeeshan is a cheerful student</title> 
       <link>http://jyoti.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=310</link> 
       <img src="images/JeeshanV.I-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/JeeshanV.I-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Jeeshan is a twelve year old boy studying in the Visually Impaired section at Amar Jyoti School. He is performing at a fourth grade level in academics. He is a cheerful child and is regular in coming to school. Jeeshan comes from an economically underprivileged family. His father is unemployed as he is visually impaired...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Saravana Kumar wants to become a doctor!</title> 
       <link>http://isha.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=32</link> 
       <img src="images/Saravana-Kumar-Isha-Vidya-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/Saravana-Kumar-Isha-Vidya-300x225.jpg" /> 
       <text>Saravana Kumar is 10 years old and has been with Isha Vidhya for just over a year.  In 2008, Saravana missed a year of school because of a head injury but he was encouraged to rejoin the school by his eldest brother, who also works as a driver at Isha Vidhya.  Saravan's father...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Venkatraj studying at the Padma Industrial School</title> 
       <link>http://padma.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=143</link> 
       <img src="images/Video-72-00m-06s.jpg" lowsrc="images/Video-72-00m-06s-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Venkatraj's brother is an automobile mechanic. Following in his brother's footsteps, Venkatraj has decided to become a motorbike repairman. He needed a motorbike repair kit to complete his studies at the Padma Industrial School. Thank you so much Benjamin for your contribution. You have enabled Venkatraj to complete his studies.</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Madhuben can now stitch and repair clothes!</title> 
       <link>http://bpa.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=505</link> 
       <img src="images/Madhuben-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/Madhuben-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Madhuben Gandabhai Patel is 60 years old and lives in Dehegam, Ahmedabad. She is a homemaker and has a sewing machine in her house. She used to take care of all the stitching needs of her family. When she developed a cataract she was unable to use her sewing machine and withdrew from most of...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Varsha is improving with help from her teachers!</title> 
       <link>http://jyoti.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=425</link> 
       <img src="images/Varsha.JPG" lowsrc="images/Varsha-480x474.jpg" /> 
       <text>Varsha is a 9 year old  girl studying in the special section at Amar Jyoti School. She suffers from cerebral palsy along with mental retardation. As a result, she is wheel chair bound. She is cheerful and enthusiastic and comes to school regularly. Varsha's family makes very little money. Her father is a helper in...</text> 
   </item>  
   <item> 
       <title>S. Dinakaran is excited to have his own Electrical Toolkit!</title> 
       <link>http://padma.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=417</link> 
       <img src="images/Dinakaran.jpg" lowsrc="images/Dinakaran-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>S. Dinakaran comes from an ambitious family, so it's no surprise that he has pursued a career in the electrical trade! Dinakaran has three brothers and one sister. His first brother works with his father on their family farm, his second brother is working on his Bachelors in Education and his third brother is completing...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Arjunan has an Electrical Toolkit!</title> 
       <link>http://padma.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=411</link> 
       <img src="images/Arjunan.jpg" lowsrc="images/Arjunan-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>S. Arjunan dropped out of school in 10th grade in order to earn the money his family needed to put his two siblings through high school.  His father, Subramanian, is a farmer and his mother, Maragatham, is a home maker.  Unfortunately, his family situation did not allow all three siblings to go to school.  Instead...</text> 
   </item>   
   <item> 
       <title>Laghubhai can see again!</title> 
       <link>http://bpa.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=432</link> 
       <img src="images/31.Laghubhai-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/31.Laghubhai-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Laghubhai is 60 years old, and lives in Bagodara Taluka, in the district of Ahmedabad. Laghubhai is a retired farm laborer and his combined family income is very low. Laghubhai developed a cataract in his left eye due to his age, but could not afford surgery. With the support of Adesh’s donation, we are able...</text> 
   </item>  
   <item> 
       <title>Vishal is learning English and Hindi!</title> 
       <link>http://jyoti.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=458</link> 
       <img src="images/Vishal_Ingle.JPG" lowsrc="images/Vishal_Ingle-451x480.jpg" /> 
       <text>Vishal is a 7 year old boy studying in 2nd grade at the Amar Jyoti campus in Gwalior.  Vishal has a pleasant personality and is regular in coming to school.  Vishal's family makes very little money. His father is a sweeper  and his mother is a homemaker.  It is the support of Shane (6 months), Vidur...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Praveen is confident that he will get a good job!</title> 
       <link>http://bpa.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=663</link> 
       <img src="images/IMG_0407-768x1024.jpg" lowsrc="images/IMG_0407-360x480.jpg" /> 
       <text>Praveen is 22 years old and has had low vision since birth. Praveen lives in the village of Thangadh in Surendranagar district. Surendranagar is located in Gujarat State in West India.  Praveen has 6 members in his family. Praveen is presently enrolled in the motor rewinding course at the Rajesh Metha Technical School for the...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Ramesh plans to give back to society as a physiotherapist</title> 
       <link>http://bpa.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=718</link> 
       <img src="images/ramesh-768x1024.jpg" lowsrc="images/ramesh-360x480.jpg" /> 
       <text>Yadav Ramesh is 22 years old and lives in Dungarpur, Rajasthan. At the age of 3, he became blind due to chicken pox. Ramesh has been associated with the Blind People's Association since 1996. After completion of 12th grade he enrolled in the physiotherapy school at BPA, where he is now in his 2nd year. Ramesh loves...</text> 
   </item>   
   <item> 
       <title>Sack gardens in the city</title> 
       <link>http://ghi.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=51</link> 
       <img src="images/Sack-gardens-in-the-city.jpg" lowsrc="images/Sack-gardens-in-the-city-225x300.jpg" /> 
       <text>Mado lives in Kigali with three children. She has a small alleyway along the side of her home, a sunny spot, though small for vegetables with poor soil. With her home garden package from Gardens for Health, Mado has filled the small space with sack gardens. Her favorite vegetable is amaranth, known as "dodo." Mado credits...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Twelve donors are supporting Pooja's tuition!</title> 
       <link>http://jyoti.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=513</link> 
       <img src="images/Pooja.jpg" lowsrc="images/Pooja-333x480.jpg" /> 
       <text>Pooja is a 13 year old girl studying in 6th grade at the Amar Jyoti School in Gwalior, India.  Gwalior is about 200 miles southeast of New Delhi.  Although Pooja is a little shy by nature, she enjoys coming to school and learning new things.  Pooja's family makes very little money. Her father earns daily...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>S. Madavan has received a welding kit!</title> 
       <link>http://padma.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=268</link> 
       <img src="images/madavan-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/madavan-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>S.Madavan is the son of Mr. Shekar, a farmer coolie and Ms. Ananthi, a home maker. He has  one younger  brother studying in 5th standard and 2 elder sisters. The first sister is studying in 9th standard and the second sister is in 8th standard. He is from Anaivadapathi village in Tiruvarur district near Ammaiyappan...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Parental involvement at Amar Jyoti school</title> 
       <link>http://jyoti.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=280</link> 
       <img src="images/Manish-Kumar-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/Manish-Kumar-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Amar Jyoti school provides unique opportunities for children with disabilities. For hearing-impaired students like Manish, 9, studying at Amar Jyoti will be a life-changing experience, providing him with an education he couldn't access at other schools. The direct involvement of the Amar Jyoti teachers has encouraged Manish to take his academics seriously. His teacher notes...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Manav follows is his sister's footsteps</title> 
       <link>http://jyoti.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=179</link> 
       <img src="images/MANAV-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/MANAV-479x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Manav is a six year old boy studying in the Nursery class at Amar Jyoti School. He is a talkative and cheerful student and always follows instructions. He takes interest in both his academics and extra-curricular activities, including group games. Manav's father has passed away, and his mother is supporting the family on a house maid's...</text> 
   </item>  
   <item> 
       <title>Vinoth is using his new welding kit!</title> 
       <link>http://padma.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=451</link> 
       <img src="images/vinoth.jpg" lowsrc="images/vinoth-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>T. Vinoth joined the welding trade at the Padma Industrial School after completing 10th grade.  Like many of his classmates, he joined the school to supplement his parents income and support his siblings. His father, Mr. Thangavel, is an agriculturist and his mother, Ms. Kamala is a home maker.  He has 2 brothers and a...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Chanchiben is now able to look at her beloved Lord Krishna with adoration</title> 
       <link>http://bpa.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=334</link> 
       <img src="images/Chanchiben-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/Chanchiben-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Chanchiben is 60 years old and lives in Sahij village, in the district of Kalol, India. She is  a housewife and lives below the  poverty line. In many villages people are not aware of  the dangers of cataracts and become needlessly blind. Chanchiben could not afford surgery even though she was aware of the consequences...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Prabhat wants to start a weaving business!</title> 
       <link>http://bpa.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=651</link> 
       <img src="images/IMG_0377-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/IMG_0377-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Prabhat Patel is 32 years old and lives in Vastrapur, Ahmedabad. At only 14 years of age, Prabhat lost his vision due to a retinal detachment and became totally blind. When Prabhat first started looking for work he had little hope. Fortunately, someone told him about the BPA Technical School and the courses provided there...</text> 
   </item>  
   <item> 
       <title>V.Rajesh is working on his electrical kit</title> 
       <link>http://padma.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=414</link> 
       <img src="images/Rajesh.jpg" lowsrc="images/Rajesh-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>V. Rajesh comes from a large family.  He has two sisters and one brother.  So many children has put a financial stress on his parents.  His father, Mr. R. Vasan, is a farm laborer and his mother, Selvi, is a home maker.  As a result, Rajesh decided to leave his traditional school, and pursue the...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Making a difference on and off the court</title> 
       <link>http://jyoti.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=386</link> 
       <img src="images/Rohit-Kr.-Pasi-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/Rohit-Kr.-Pasi-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Rohit is a fourteen year old boy who loves to play basketball. Rohit also has polio, but he hasn't let that stop him from getting involved in sports at Amar Jyoti school. In the six years he has attended Amar Jyoti, his teachers have noticed a steadily increasing level of confidence in Rohit, both in...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Pirubhai can take care of his buffaloes again!</title> 
       <link>http://bpa.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=502</link> 
       <img src="images/Pirubhai-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/Pirubhai-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Pirubhai Chotubhai Diwan is 70 years old. He makes his living doing farm work with the help of his two buffaloes. When he developed a cataract,  Pirubhai had a lot of trouble taking care of his buffaloes and maintaining his fields. He was identified by BPA field workers who visited his village and he was...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>S. Alwin Raj is working with his Welding Kit!</title> 
       <link>http://padma.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=265</link> 
       <img src="images/alwinraj-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/alwinraj-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>S. Alwin Raj is the eldest son of Mr.Vaduvaiyan, a farmer coolie and Ms.Pavunammal, a home maker. He has 2 brothers. One brother is studying in 7th standard and the other brother is in 5th standard.  He has no sisters. He is from Sengalipuram village in Tiruvarur district, which is 3kms away from Manjakkudi...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>How surgery changed Bababhai's life</title> 
       <link>http://bpa.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=283</link> 
       <img src="images/Bababhai-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/Bababhai-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>Imagine losing your sight. This is what happened to 72 year-old Bababhai. He could no longer see the faces of his family members. He could not longer move around on his own. Bababhai grew introverted, distant from his family and friends. He was constantly depressed and felt that his life was no longer worth living...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>David Joshi has found a new world</title> 
       <link>http://bpa.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=492</link> 
       <img src="images/IMG_0311-768x1024.jpg" lowsrc="images/IMG_0311-360x480.jpg" /> 
       <text>David is 18 years old and has limited vision. He lives in the ATC Hostel for the Blind. He was born in Rajasthan and now his whole family has moved to Ahmedabad. In David’s family there are 5 members. His father is a priest in the temple. David studied in a  school  for the sighted until 8th...</text> 
   </item>  
   <item> 
       <title>Clementine and an Avocado</title> 
       <link>http://ghi.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=57</link> 
       <img src="images/Clementine-and-an-Avocado1.jpg" lowsrc="images/Clementine-and-an-Avocado1-195x300.jpg" /> 
       <text>With support from Gardens for Health, Clementine was given an avocado seedling, a moringa seedling, and a mixture of vegetable seeds, like carrots, beets, swiss chard, and spinach for her home garden. Her one year old son was recently diagnosed with severe acute malnutrition, and while he is now, fortunately, recovering, growing nutritious food for...</text> 
   </item> 
   <item> 
       <title>Making a difference!</title> 
       <link>http://padma.dev1.seeyourimpact.com/?p=262</link> 
       <img src="images/pandian-1024x768.jpg" lowsrc="images/pandian-480x360.jpg" /> 
       <text>R.Pandiyan is the son of Mr. G. Ravikumar, a farmer coolie and Ms. Mariyammal, a home maker. He has a no brothers, but he has a sister studying in 10th standard. He is from Simizhi village in Tiruvarur district, 5kms away from Manjakkudi . His family income is Rs 12000 per annum.  As a result...</text> 
   </item> 
</root>